Civil Service Employees Association, Inc. (CSEA), American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME) Local 1000 Records apap015
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Images, 1947-2013; 10; 2.8 cubic ft.
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) J.N...., 2000
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) members..., 2000
  - A Pataki zero dollar reserve note floats around on..., 2000
  - Daniel Campbell riding in a truck pulling a float..., 2000
  - Congressman Michael McNulty attending an..., 2000
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) members..., 2001 March
  - Grand Island, New York, Animal Control Officer and..., 2007 March
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 1982 April
  - Members of Civil Service Employees Association and..., 2001 April
  - Unidentified Civil Service Employees Association..., 2001 April
  - Former First Lady Rosalynn Carter was the guest of..., 2006 April
  - Daycare provider Sally Heater, from East Syracuse,..., 2007 April
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) members..., 2007 April
  - A large crowd of unidentified Civil Service..., 1991 May
  - A group of unidentified Civil Service Employees..., 1995 May
  - A Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2002 May
  - Suffolk County, New York daycare provider Roxanne..., 2007 May
  - Group provider Cheryl Oare with some of the..., 2007 May
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) Taconic..., 2007 May
  - Civil Service Employee Association (CSEA)..., 1997 June
  - A Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2002 June
  - Unidentified Civil Service Employees Association..., 2007 June
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2007 June
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2000 July
  - Two unidentified Civil Service Employees..., 2006 July
  - Suffolk County, New York, Police Officer Robert..., 2006 July
  - Unidentified Civil Service Employees Association..., 2001 August
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)'s..., 2006 August
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2006 August
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2006 August
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) Central..., 2007 August
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) members..., 1994 August 16
  - Candidates for top office in the State..., 1970 September
  - President Jimmy Carter waves to the crowd at the..., 1980 September
  - President Jimmy Carter laughs at a comment by..., 1980 September
  - John F. Kennedy Jr., a guest speaker at the 1992..., 1992 September
  - Presidential candidate Bill Clinton, a guest..., 1992 September
  - Presidential candidate Bill Clinton addressing the..., 1992 September
  - Unidentified Civil Service Employees Association..., 1998 September
  - Five Civil Service Employees Association..., 1999 September
  - New York Governor George E. Pataki observes a..., 2001 September
  - Unidentified Civil Service Employees Association..., 2001 September
  - State Emergency Management Office workers were..., 2001 September
  - Unidentified Civil Service Employees Association..., 2001 September
  - University at Albany President Kermit Hall, Civil..., 2005 September
  - Faces of The Work Force are photos taken by Civil..., 2005 September
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) Western..., 2005 September
  - New York State candidate for governor Eliot..., 2006 September
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) members..., 2006 September
  - CBS Early Show anchor Hannah Storm posing with..., 2006 September
  - Unidentified Civil Service Employees Association..., 2007 September
  - New York State Police Color Guard opening the 2007..., 2007 September
  - New York State Comptroller Thomas DiNapoli, second..., 2007 September
  - A news clipping from the Utica, NY Observer-..., 1966 September 17
  - Officers of Oneida (New York) County chapter of..., 1973 September 25
  - New York State Governor George E. Pataki signing..., Undated
  - AFL-CIO Secretary-Treasurer Richard Trumka fires..., Undated
  - Institution teachers stage a demonstration on the..., 1970
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 1979
  - Gubernatorial candidate Mario Cuomo, front, second..., 1982
  - New York Governor Mario Cuomo meets with Civil..., 1983
  - Governor Mario Cuomo accepting the Civil Service..., 1986
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)'s 1994...
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) Board..., 1997
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)'s 1998...
  - Members of the Civil Service Employees Association..., 1998
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2001
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member,..., 2006
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2009 January
  - Pressure from the Civil Service Employees..., 2008 October
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member..., 2008 October
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)'s 2008..., 2008 November
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) members..., 2008 November
  - Members of Civil Service Employees Association..., 2008 November
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) Central..., 2008 November
  - Across New York, Civil Service Employees..., 2008 December
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) members..., 2008 February
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2008 February
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member,..., 2008 February
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) Long..., 2009 February
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)'s Port..., 2008 March
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)/Child..., 2008 March
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)'s..., 2008 March
  - Lisa Bohannon, at work in the Unified Court System..., 2009 March
  - Across New York state, Civil Service Employees..., 2009 March
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member,..., 2008 April
  - Barbara Rustin, president of the Civil Service..., 2008 April
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) Western..., 2008 April
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member,..., 2008 April
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)'s..., 2009 April
  - Across New York state, Civil Service Employees..., 2009 April
  - New York State Governor David Paterson, plugging..., 2009 April
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2009 April
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2009 April
  - Steven Myers, vice president of the Civil Service..., 2009 April
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)'s..., 2008 May
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)'s..., 2008 May
  - Fighting swine flu on all fronts: Civil Service..., 2009 May
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member,..., 2009 May
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) Clinton..., 2008 June
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) Clinton..., 2008 June
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member..., 2008 June
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member,..., 2008 August
  - Michael Asencio, who works for the Westchester..., 2008 September
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) members..., 2008 September
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) members..., 2008 September
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) members..., 2008 September
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) members..., 2008 September
  - Florence Cohen, a keyboard specialist for the..., 2002 January
  - Marian Hrycak, a investigator for the state Tax..., 2002 January
  - A preschool student in Manlius, Onondaga County,..., 2002 January
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) Long..., 2007 January
  - Mattituck-Cutchogue (New York) School District..., 2007 January
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2007 January
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) cartoon..., 2008 January
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member,..., 2008 January
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2008 January 23
  - Governor David Paterson's announcement of..., 2009 January 23
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 1984 October
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) members..., 1987 October
  - New York City Mayor Rudolph Giuliani welcoming..., 1996 October
  - Marlene Neal, Civil Service Employees Association..., 2005 October
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2005 October
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2005 October
  - Portrait of Civil Service Employees Association..., 2005 October
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) Delware..., 2005 October
  - The Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2007 October
  - United States Senator Hillary Clinton speaks at an..., 2001 November
  - Delegates to Civil Service Employees Association..., 2001 November
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2002 November
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) members..., 2004 November
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) members..., 2005 November
  - Cathy Barretta, the Civil Service Employees..., 2006 November
  - The Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)'s..., 2006 November
  - Brianne Nobis, a global Messenger for Special..., 2006 November
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member..., 2006 November
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) retiree..., 2006 November
  - Civil Service Employyes Association (CSEA), local..., 1990 December
  - Gowanda Psychiatric Center employees celebrating..., 1990 December
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member,..., 2005 December
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member,..., 2005 December
  - Connetquot School District Operations Unit..., 2005 December
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member..., 2007 December
  - A Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) photo..., 2007 December
  - The Oneida, NY Chapter of the Civil Service..., 1972 December 1
  - New York State Governor Thomas E. Dewey (right),..., 1947
  - Unidentified psychiatric hospital employees enjoy..., 1948
  - Psychiatric Aide Award winners with Acting..., 1955
  - Viewers looked in on a New York State School for..., 1957
  - Safety of patients and employees in the Department..., 1959
  - Among the officials and guests at the 1964 Hotel...
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 1980
  - Unidentified Civil Service Employees Association..., 1980
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 1982
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) members..., 1990
  - Theresa Canestrari and Peter Mendez are sworn in..., 1990
  - Unidentified Civil Service Employees Association..., 1990
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) Region..., 1990
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) SUNY..., 1995
  - A group of unidentified Civil Service Employees..., 1995
  - Unidentified members of the Civil Service..., 1995
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) members..., 1995
  - More than 1600 Binghamton area Civil Service..., 1995
  - New York State Senator Tom Libous speaks to a..., 1995
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) Region..., 1995
  - Karen Gambino of St. Mary's School for the Deaf,..., 1996
  - United States Representative Richard Gephardt..., 1998
  - The Reverend Al Sharpton speaks into a bullhorn..., 1999
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) members..., 2005 February
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member,..., 2006 February
  - State lawmakers, including Senate Majority Leader..., 2006 February
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) Western..., 2006 February
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member,..., 2006 February
  - Cheryl M. Perkins, Library Clerk at SUNY Health..., 2007 February
  - Kathleen Cronin, head of children's services for..., 2007 February
  - United States Congresswoman Carolyn McCarthy with..., 2000
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2000
  - AFL-CIO President John Sweeney speaks at an Civil..., 2000
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) members..., 2000
  - John Shepherd at an Civil Service Employees..., 2000
  - AFSCME President Gerry McEntee sits in a panel..., 2000
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2000
  - Danny Donohue serves as the 22nd president of the..., 2000
  - Buffalo Mayor Anthony Masiello speaks at a Civil..., 2000
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2003
  - Thousands of unidentified Civil Service Employees..., 1975 March
  - Two Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 1997 March
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) members..., 2007 March
  - A graphic depicting the New York state Office of..., 2007 March
  - Day care provider and Civil Service Employees..., 2007 March
  - A group of unidentified Civil Service Employees..., 2001 April
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member,..., 2006 April
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2006 April
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2007 April
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2007 April
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) Central..., 2007 April
  - A clipping from the Syracuse Herald-Journal..., 1964 April 31
  - Unidentified Civil Service Employees Association..., 1999 May
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member..., 2007 May
  - Utica New York Chapter Meeting of the Civil..., 1965 May 3
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member..., 2005 June
  - Members of the 90 Church Street Labor Coalition,..., 2007 June
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2007 June
  - Oneida County, NY Chapter of Civil Service..., 1967 June 23
  - Irene Carr being interviewed by Cable 6 TV,..., 1994 July
  - The cover of the July 2000 edition of Civil..., 2000 July
  - Tom DiNapoli speaks to a crowd of unidentified..., 2001 August
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) retiree..., 2006 August
  - Onondaga County Executive candidate Bill..., 2007 August
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) Capital..., 2007 August
  - Enthusiastic supporters greet United States..., 2007 August
  - President Jimmy Carter waves to the crowd at the..., 1980 September
  - Unidentified Civil Service Employees Association..., 1992 September
  - John F. Kennedy Jr. addressing the delegates at..., 1992 September
  - Presidential candidate Bill Clinton speaking with..., 1992 September
  - Presidential Candidate Bill Clinton and Civil..., 1992 September
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) members..., 1999 September
  - New York Governor George Pataki meets with state..., 2001 September
  - Unidentified Civil Service Employees Association..., 2001 September
  - President Jimmy Carter addresses delegates to the..., 2004 September
  - From left, Civil Service Employees Association..., 2005 September
  - Erie County Medical Center is known throughout..., 2006 September
  - Jim Kelly, John J. Kelly Jr.'s son, holding a..., 2006 September
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2007 September
  - New York State Comptroller Thomas DiNapoli,..., 2007 September
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member,..., 2007 September
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) Olympic..., 2007 September
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) members..., 2002 September 11
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2001 September 18
  - Former U.S. President Bill Clinton, left, at the..., 2001 November 1
  - Salamanca, New York, Police officers Chris..., Undated
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member..., Undated
  - Former Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 1970
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) Long..., 1980
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) Western..., 1982
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 1982
  - U.S. Senator Daniel Patrick Moynihan, left, reads..., 1987
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)'s 1994...
  - This Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 1995
  - An unidentified Civil Service Employees..., 1999
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)'s 2002...
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) members..., 2009 January
  - Dispatchers, from left, Gregory Schmid, David..., 2008 October
  - Goshen Secure Center Local Secretary Amber..., 2008 November
  - Shirley Singletary, board vice president for the..., 2008 November
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) Chemung..., 2008 November
  - Nearly 40 Civil Service Employees Association..., 2008 November
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)'s 2008..., 2008 November
  - Across New York, Civil Service Employees..., 2008 December
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2008 December
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) members..., 2008 February
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member,..., 2008 February
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)'s..., 2008 March
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2009 March
  - From left, New York Labor-Religion Coalition..., 2009 March
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member,..., 2009 March
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member..., 2009 March
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2008 April
  - Family members of Civil Service Employees..., 2008 April
  - Somewhat reluctant, but being a good sport, Civil..., 2009 April
  - Across New York state, Civil Service Employees..., 2009 April
  - Judiciary Local activist Judy DiPaola, Rochester..., 2009 April
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) Suffolk..., 2009 April
  - Across New York state, Civil Service Employees..., 2009 April
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2008 May
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) Capital..., 2009 May
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) members..., 2008 June
  - The 2008 Civil Service Employees Association..., 2008 June
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)'s..., 2008 June
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)'s..., 2008 July
  - Workers at the Civil Service Employees Association..., 2008 August
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) members..., 2008 September
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) members..., 2008 September
  - AFSCME President Gerald McEntee expresses..., 2008 September
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) members..., 2008 September
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) members..., 2008 September
  - John J. Kelly Jr. with New York State Governor..., 1954 January
  - Harry Goody, a supply assistant for the state..., 2002 January
  - Harry Goody, a supply assistant for the state..., 2002 January
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) members..., 2004 January
  - Faces of The Work Force are photos taken by Civil..., 2005 January
  - Cartoon depicting New York State Governor Eliot..., 2007 January
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2007 January
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)'s New..., 2008 January
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member,..., 2008 January
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 1984 October
  - Negotiating team leaders and representatives from..., 1984 October
  - Two unidentified Civil Service Employees..., 1987 October
  - Two Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 1987 October
  - The notice was part of a Civil Service Employees..., 1997 October
  - A group of unidentified Civil Service Employees..., 1997 October
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) SUNY..., 2000 October
  - A crowd of Civil Service Employees Association..., 2001 October
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) Labor..., 2005 October
  - Portrair of Civil Service Employees Association..., 2005 October
  - A Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2005 October
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member,..., 2006 October
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member..., 2006 October
  - An aerial photo of Civil Service Employees..., 2001 October 11
  - United States Senator Hillary Rodham Clinton..., 2002 November
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2002 November
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member..., 2005 November
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member..., 2005 November
  - Civil Service Employees Association..., 2006 November
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member..., 2006 November
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) Madison..., 2006 November
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)'s..., 2006 November
  - The military decorations of the Civil Service..., 2006 November
  - From left, New York State Assemblyman Paul Tonko,..., 2006 November
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member,..., 2007 November
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member..., 2005 December
  - Connetquot school bus driver Barbara Sakaris waits..., 2005 December
  - The Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2006 December
  - Ed Burkhart, a Civil Service Employees Association..., 2007 December
  - Dr. James I. Wyer, Jr. served as the 4th president..., 1922
  - William F. McDonough served as the 10th president..., 1929-1934
  - The Department of Mental Hygiene saw recreation as..., 1949
  - Former patient Audrey Cole guides March of..., 1955
  - Holiday celebrations and traditions are high spots..., 1956
  - With growing public confidence in mental..., 1958
  - Highlight of "Psychiatric Aide Day" honoring award..., 1960
  - Flyer created to promote the Civil Service..., 1964
  - Clinton Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 1972
  - Newly elected officers of the Marcy State Hospital..., 1973
  - Then Lieutenant Governor Mario Cuomo speaking at..., 1981
  - This Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 1985
  - Senator Joseph Holland, Assemblyman Alex Gromack,..., 1990
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) Long..., 1990
  - New York State Assemblyman Clarence Norman..., 1995
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member..., 1995
  - New York State Assemblyman Francisco Diaz meets..., 1995
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) local..., 1995
  - Civil Service Eployees Association(CSEA) Broome..., 1995
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) Ulster..., 1995
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 1995
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 1995
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)'s..., 1998
  - Bob Maccar of Civil Service Employees Association..., 1998
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 1982 February
  - News reporters and Civil Service Employees..., 1982 February
  - Faces of The Work Force are photos taken by Civil..., 2005 February
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) members..., 2006 February
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)'s..., 2007 February
  - In one of the largest demonstrations ever held in..., 1991 February 5
  - Members of the Civil Service Employees Association..., 2000
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) Sidney..., 2000
  - Civil Service Employess Association (CSEA),..., 2000
  - George Boncoraglio (at left), Civil Service..., 2000
  - Members of the Teamsters Local 294 give the thumbs..., 2000
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2000
  - Frank Marco, Executive Director of the Fiscal..., 2000
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2000
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2000
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2003
  - Unidentifed Civil Service Employees Association..., 2004 March
  - Tioga County Department of Social Service Foster..., 2007 March
  - Effective Communication Facilitator Elizabeth..., 2007 March